<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food on Staff Engineer @Mailchimp</title>
    <link>https://bobstrecansky.com/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food on Staff Engineer @Mailchimp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 04:03:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bobstrecansky.com/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sous Vide Fillet with Sesame Asparagus and Roasted Thyme Potatoes</title>
      <link>https://bobstrecansky.com/food/2020/04/25/sous-vide-fillet-with-sesame-asparagus-and-roasted-thyme-potatoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 04:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bobstrecansky.com/food/2020/04/25/sous-vide-fillet-with-sesame-asparagus-and-roasted-thyme-potatoes/</guid>
      <description>My wife likes steak. It&amp;rsquo;s been her favorite meal since she was little. I thought I should treat her to her favorite dinner on a Friday night (It&amp;rsquo;s been fun to cook a little bit more during our self-quarantine). I&amp;rsquo;ve been attempting to perfect my sous vide fillet, and I&amp;rsquo;m getting pretty proud of it. The secret ingredient to a fillet (in my wife&amp;rsquo;s eyes) is Dale&amp;rsquo;s Seasonsing, which is proclaimed on their website to be the &amp;ldquo;#1 Marinade in the Nation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spicy Chicken Sausage</title>
      <link>https://bobstrecansky.com/food/2020/04/24/spicy-chicken-sausage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 01:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bobstrecansky.com/food/2020/04/24/spicy-chicken-sausage/</guid>
      <description>Tonight I concocted a spicy andouille chicken sausage over white rice and steamed, raw honey glazed carrots. This worked as a combination better than I thought it would. The spicy from the chicken sausage, the slight sweet from the raw honey, and the buttery smooth rice worked nicely together. I&amp;rsquo;ll certainly be making this again in the future!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caulipower Pizza</title>
      <link>https://bobstrecansky.com/food/2020/04/23/caulipower-pizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 02:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bobstrecansky.com/food/2020/04/23/caulipower-pizza/</guid>
      <description>My wife is a huge pizza fan. I’ve been trying to not eat like a jerk, so we’ve found that cauliflower pizza can often be a good middle ground for both of us. It’s healthy, it tastes 75% as good as pizza, and it helps me to avoid the dad bod.
We tried out Caulipower’s Veggie Pizza tonight. We added prosciutto, just to take the vegetarian edge off.
The verdict?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>